https://insomniacmagazine.com/gdpr-privacy-notice/

Sign inHomeAboutPodcastStoreMarketingContact Us Sign in Welcome!Log into your accountyour usernameyour password
Forgot your password?GDPR Privacy Notice Password recoveryRecover your passwordyour email
Search Sign in / Join
Sign inWelcome! Log into your accountyour usernameyour password Forgot your password? Get helpGDPR Privacy NoticePassword recoveryRecover your passwordyour email A password will be e-mailed to you.
Insomniac Magazine HomeAboutPodcastStoreMarketingContact UsHome
GDPR Privacy Notice GDPR Privacy NoticePrivacy Policy for Insomniac MagazineAt Insomniac Magazine, accessible from https://insomniacmagazine.com/, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Insomniac Magazine and how we use it.If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)We are a Data Controller of your information.Insomniac Magazine legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Information we collect and the specific context in which we collect the information:Insomniac Magazine needs to perform a contract with youYou have given Insomniac Magazine permission to do soProcessing your personal information is in Insomniac Magazine legitimate interestsInsomniac Magazine needs to comply with the lawInsomniac Magazine will retain your personal information only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your information to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our policies. Our Privacy Policy was generated with the help of GDPR Privacy Policy Generator and the Privacy Policy Generator.If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. If you wish to be informed what Personal Information we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.The right of rectification.The right to object.The right of restriction.The right to data portabilityThe right to withdraw consentLog FilesInsomniac Magazine follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.Cookies and Web BeaconsLike any other website, Insomniac Magazine uses ‘cookies’. These cookies are used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.Privacy PoliciesYou may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Insomniac Magazine.Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Insomniac Magazine, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.Note that Insomniac Magazine has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.Third Party Privacy PoliciesInsomniac Magazine’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. You may find a complete list of these Privacy Policies and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?Children’s InformationAnother part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.Insomniac Magazine does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.Online Privacy Policy OnlyOur Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Insomniac Magazine. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.ConsentBy using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.Who we areOur website address is: https://insomniacmagazine.com. What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact formsWe obtain clear and unambiguous consent in advance of collecting personal data that is now considered essential in terms of protecting privacy rights. Before sending you info via our contact form (we use Contact Form 7 plugin) be sure to check and accept our privacy policy.CookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year. If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser. When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed. If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day. Embedded content from other websites Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsHow long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue. For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.LISTEN TO OUR PODCASTGET THE STEEZABOUT USSince 1996, Insomniac Magazine has been dedicated to quality Hip Hop coverage and support. #hiphopculture #hiphop #hiphopmusic
Contact UsFOLLOW US
HomeAboutPodcastStoreMarketingContact Us © Insomniac MagazineWe are using cookies to give you the best experience on our website.You can find out more about which cookies we are using or switch them off in settings. Accept
Sign Up To Our NewsletterNameEmail
Close GDPR Cookie Settings
Privacy Overview
Strictly Necessary Cookies Powered by  GDPR Cookie Compliance Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies so that we can provide you with the best user experience possible. Cookie information is stored in your browser and performs functions such as recognising you when you return to our website and helping our team to understand which sections of the website you find most interesting and useful. Strictly Necessary CookiesStrictly Necessary Cookie should be enabled at all times so that we can save your preferences for cookie settings.
Enable or Disable Cookies
If you disable this cookie, we will not be able to save your preferences. This means that every time you visit this website you will need to enable or disable cookies again. Enable All Save Settings
